Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Dick Thornburgh Papers, Series XIX. Videos
1978-2010
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Thornburgh, Dick
AIS.1998.30.19
271 items
The Dick Thornburgh video collection, consists of 251 videos from the years 1978-1991, 2003, 2009, which begin with Thornburgh's gubernatorial campaign in 1978, and continue up to and including his campaign for U.S. Senate in 1991. There are 55 videos (14.5 hours total) available here online. Subjects and events include, for example: campaign ads, inaugurals, budget addresses, appearances on McNeil/Lehrer both as Governor and Attorney General, news conferences from the week of the accident at Three Mile Island, a brief clip of the welcoming by Governor Thornburgh of Pope John Paul II to Philadelphia, 1979, Attorney General's announcement of Banca Nazionale del Lavoro (BNL) related indictments, and the first anniversary of the signing of the Americans With Disabilities Act (ADA). Digital reproductions of portions of the collection are available online.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dick Thornburgh, February 27, 1998.
Previous Citation
Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932-, AIS.1998.30, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
United States -- Politics and government -- 20th century; Pennsylvania -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Political campaigns -- Pennsylvania; Personal papers; Government; Politics; Environment; Three Mile Island Nuclear Power Plant (Pa.); United States. Attorney-General; United States. Congress. Senate -- Elections; Pennsylvania. Governor -- Elections; Pennsylvania. Governor (1979-1987: Thornburgh); Thornburgh, Ginny (Judson); Thornburgh, Dick
- Video, 1978-2010; XIX.
  Scope and Contents note
  The Thornburgh archive at the University of Pittsburgh has 547 videos from the years 1978-1991, which begin with Thornburgh's gubernatorial campaign in 1978, and continue up to and including his campaign for U.S. Senate in 1991. Since that time, both from Thornburgh's position as Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations and in his ongoing career, there have been no video additions to the collection. All 547 videos have been reformatted for preservation and 55 videos (14.5 hours total) are available here online.
  Subjects and events include, for example: campaign ads, inaugurals, budget addresses, appearances on McNeil/Lehrer both as Governor and Attorney General, news conferences from the week of the accident at Three Mile Island, Martin Luther King Day events, Governor's Awards for Excellence in the Arts, Distinguished Service Medal to General Matthew B. Ridgeway, a brief clip of the welcoming by Governor Thornburgh of Pope John Paul II to Philadelphia, 1979, Attorney General's announcement of Banca Nazionale del Lavoro (BNL) related indictments, and the first anniversary of the signing of the Americans With Disabilities Act (ADA).
  It should be noted that at the time Thornburgh became Governor of Pennsylvania, in 1979, videotapes were comparatively early in their use and quality. In fact, Commonwealth Media was formally established by Governor Thornburgh only after the accident at Three Mile Island, which dramatically exemplified the usefulness of visual documentation of major occurrences, news conferences, and events.
  Selection of videos available here online is intended to portray an array of events and issues that are both visually interesting and have representative and significant content. In some cases the quality is less than excellent, but the content merited inclusion. Videos here are in low/high bandwidth in Windows Media and Quicktime formats
  - Campaign for Governor, 1979; 1.
    - Thornburgh for Governor campaign ads (Primary and General elections) [online], 1978 (Box 1600, Video DTV 001)
    - League of Women Voters' Thornburgh / Flaherty Debate #2, October 10, 1978 (Box 1600, Video DTV 002)
    - PPTN: Governor Thornburgh Inauguration Ceremony [online], January 16, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 003)
  - Governor, 1979-1987; 2.
    - PBS: Transition: A Governor Takes Office, February 4, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 004)
    - WTPA: Tour of Governor's Home and Interview with Governor and Ginny, May 9, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 005)
    - Governor's Speech to Joint Session of the Pennsylvania Legislature [online], October 1, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 006)
    - Governor Greeting Pope John Paul II in Pope's first visit to Philadelphia [online], October 9, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 007)
    - Lancaster Town Meeting with Governor, December 18, 1979; 2 tapes (Box 1600, Video DTV 008 009)
    - Marcia Kaplan Interviews: Jay Waldman and Paul Critchlow, December 21, 1979 December 28, 1979 (Box 1600, Video DTV 010)
    - Marsha Kaplan Interviews: Governor and Lieutenant Governor, January, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 011)
    - WITF "Newsmakers" John Baer Host: Roundtable Questions and Answers with the Governor, January 21, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 012)
    - WPVI: "First Ladies" Series with Ginny Thornburgh, February 26, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 013)
    - First annual Distinguished Artists Award to Jimmy Stewart, May 1, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 014)
    - PA Distinguished Service Medal awarded to General Matthew B. Ridgeway [online], June 6, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 015)
    - PPTN: "Call the Governor: PA Town Meeting"; John Dimsdale host, June 13, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 016)
    - PPTN: "People's Business" regarding Promoting Small Business, July 4, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 017)
    - PPTN: "People's Business" regarding Coal in PA, Liquor Control Board, and other topics, July 18, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 018)
    - WPVI-Channel 6 Philadelphia: Republican Governors Association, November 17, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 019)
    - Coal Pier 124 Opening in Philadelphia, December 18, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 020)
    - WITF "Newsmakers" John Baer Host: Questions and Answers to the Governor, January 23, 1980 (Box 1600, Video DTV 021)
    - Governor's News Conference regarding reforms of Liquor Control Board (LCB) and abolishing State Store System, Harrisburg [online], January 28, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 022)
    - The Governor's Budget Address, February 3, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 023)
    - PA Charter Proclamation, March 4, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 024)
    - News Conference, Philadelphia, regarding SEPTA Strike, April 3, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 025)
    - Arnold Palmer: PA Promotion, Pittsburgh, April 13, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 026)
    - Taiwanese Contract Signing regarding purchase contracts with PA companies, May 1, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 027)
    - PA Distinguished Artists Award to James Michener, May 5, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 028)
    - WQLN: Choices for PA, May 24, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 029)
    - American Legion Convention: speech, July 11, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 030)
    - National Governors Conference (NGC): Transportation Meeting, August 10, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 031)
    - News Conference: Anti-Crime Legislation, September 16, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 032)
    - Capitol Building Rededication: 75th Anniversary, October 19, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 033)
    - Pittsburgh Parkway East Reopening and Ribbon cutting Ceremonies, October 21, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 034)
    - News Conference: Pittsburgh Transportation Projects, October 28, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 035)
    - News Conference regarding Lottery Fund and increased Senior Citizen Benefits, November 10, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 036)
    - PPTN: "Call the Governor: PA Town Meeting"; John Dimsdale Host, November 11, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 037)
    - PA Highway Conference, Pittsburgh: speech, December 9, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 038)
    - PA Highway Conference, Pittsburgh: PennDOT Secretary Larson speech, December 9, 1981 (Box 1600, Video DTV 039)
    - PBS: "MacNeil Lehrer Report" regarding New Federalism [online], January 27, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 040)
    - KYW-TV: "City Lights" regarding Black Issues, Governor, January 30, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 041)
    - Budget Address to the Legislature, February 9, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 042)
    - Thornburgh Re-Election Announcement; Franklin Plaza, Philadelphia, Pa., March 2, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 043)
    - Thornburgh Crime Bill Signing (5 Year Mandatory Sentencing for Violent Crimes), April 23, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 044)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Final Budget Address to Joint Session of Pennsylvania Legislature [online], February 4, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 045a)
    - Reelection Campaign Fundraiser Luncheon: President Reagan speaker, May 14, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 045b)
    - PA Distinguished Artists Award to Marion Anderson, June 8, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 046)
    - CNN: "Getting Tough on Crime", July 14, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 047)
    - Thornburgh Inauguration and Celebratory Events [online], January 18, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 051)
    - WPHL: "Profile" Interview regarding Commonwealth, African American Relations, Appointments, And Ben Franklin Partnership, February 11, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 052)
    - PPTN: "Call the Governor" PA Town Meeting; Mackenzie Carpenter Host, May 17, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 053)
    - Speech to National Bridge Conference, June 1, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 054)
    - News Conference: Chesapeake Bay, June 2, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 055)
    - WHTM: Marcia Kaplan Interviews Roy Zimmerman, Ginny Thornburgh, Dr. Morrison, and Governor Thornburgh, December, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 056)
    - CBS: Governor and Ginny Thornburgh in China, December 1, 1983 (Box 1600, Video DTV 057)
    - Martin Luther King Day Observance and Awards Luncheon with Governor and Coretta King, Philadelphia [online], January 16, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 058)
    - Budget Address to Legislature, February 7, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 059)
    - PBS: "MacNeil Lehrer Report" regarding the Federal Deficit [online], July 31, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 060)
    - Holiday Driving PSA with Kendall Leigh Thornburgh, November 26, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 061)
    - PA Tourism Promotions, December 10, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 062)
    - Budget Address to Legislature, February 2, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 063)
    - PBS: "MacNeil Lehrer Report" regarding the Federal Budget Impasse with Governors Thornburgh and Cuomo [online], February 25, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 064)
    - WHYY: "In Person" with Governor, April 17, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 065)
    - PBS: "MacNeil Lehrer Newshour" regarding Reagan's Tax Reform Plan, June 6, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 066)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony: Bainbridge Street Bridge, Sunbury PA, July 12, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 067)
    - Aldan Elementary School: Students' Interview with Governor, January, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 068)
    - Budget Address to Legislature, February 4, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 069)
    - PBS: "MacNeil-Lehrer Report" regarding Federal Budget '87 with Governors Thornburgh and Clinton [online], February 5, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 070)
    - Visit to Boy Scouts and Girl Scouts: Governor reading story about William Penn, March 4, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 071)
    - Speech to Financial Executives Institute (FEI) regarding "Major Business and Economic Issues Affecting Pennsylvania and Philadelphia" [online], May 1, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 072)
    - Governor's Awards for Excellence in the Arts: Hazlett Memorial Awards [online], June 2, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 073)
    - Rededication of PA Memorial at the Gettysburg Battlefield: remarks, July 1, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 074)
    - Interview with Dick Thornburgh: multiple issues, November 12, 1986; 2 videotapes (parts 1 and 2). (Box 1600, Video DTV 075 076)
    - Bainbridge Street Bridge Dedication, Sunbury, PA, November 24, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 077)
    - Larry Kane Interview regarding Welfare Reform: Governor and Ginny Thornburgh, December 1, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 078)
    - Pennsylvania Tourism Commercials [online], 1979-1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 079)
    - Conversations with the Governor #1: Education/Agenda for Excellence with Robert Wilburn, September 12, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 080)
    - Conversations with the Governor #2: Transportation with Secretary Thomas Larson, October 21, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 081)
    - Conversations with the Governor #3: Drug and Alcohol Abuse with Dick Wetherbee and Lucile Flemming, November 18, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 082)
    - Conversations with the Governor #4: Liquor Control Board with Senators Greenleaf and Kelly, December 5, 1984 (Box 1600, Video DTV 083)
    - Conversations with the Governor #5: with Nicholas Benedictus, January 10, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 084)
    - Conversations with the Governor #6: Economic Development and Jobs with Secretary James Pickard and L. Jack Bradt, February 6, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 085)
    - Conversations with the Governor #7: 1985 Budget Address, February 13, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 086)
    - Conversations with the Governor #8: Economic Development and Community Conservation with Secretary Shirley Dennis and Mayors Pfuhl and Althaus, April 1, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 087)
    - Conversations with the Governor #9: Travel and Tourism; State Parks with Chris Umble and Ned Book and Bill Forrey, May 19, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 088)
    - Conversations with the Governor #10: Handicapped with Jennifer Howse, G. Lowe, and G. Makuch, June 16, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 089)
    - Conversations with the Governor #11: Senior Citizen Programs with Secretary Alma Jacobs, July 21, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 090)
    - Conversations with the Governor #12: Job Training with Mike Aker and Marvin Berger, August 18, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 091)
    - Conversations with the Governor #13: Welfare with Secretary Walter Cohen and Don Stovall, September 22, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 092)
    - Conversations with the Governor #14: Agriculture with Secretary Grubb, Obie Snider, and Hugh Miller, October 20, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 093)
    - Conversations with the Governor #15: Health with Secretary Muller, P. Boyer, and George Grode, November 17, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 094)
    - Conversations with the Governor #16: Education with Secretary K. Wright, N. Semple, and K. Evans, December 22, 1985 (Box 1600, Video DTV 095)
    - Conversations with the Governor #17: Taxes/Budget with Secretary Jim Scheiner and Charles Potter, January 19, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 096)
    - Conversations with the Governor #18: 1986 Budget Address, February 16, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 097)
    - Conversations with the Governor #19: Emergencies with Nick Steptzoff, John Patton, PEMA, and Gen. Dick Scott, March 16, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 098)
    - Conversations with the Governor #20: Veterans with A. DiLoretto, T. Hertzler, and D. Swartz, April 20, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 099)
    - Conversations with the Governor #21: Council on Arts and PHMC with Diana Rose, L. Frantz, Larry Tise, and G. Tapper, May 18, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 100)
    - Conversations with the Governor #22: Economic Development with Walt Plosila, P. Likins, George Werner, and B. Logue, June 15, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 101)
    - Conversations with the Governor #23: Mental Illness and the Homeless with Dr. Nelson, Sheila Stacks, Trevor Ferrell, and Robert Williams, July 20, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 102)
    - Conversations with the Governor #24: Workings of State Government with Secretaries Bittenbender, Dr. Wright, and Baran, August 17, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 103)
    - Conversations with the Governor #25: Infrastructure with Secretary Thomas Larson and Secretary Nick DeBenedictis, September 12, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 104)
    - Conversations with the Governor #26: Law Enforcement and Justice with Commissioners Jay Cochran and Glen Jeffers, October 7, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 105)
    - Conversations with the Governor #27: Virginia Judson Thornburgh, November 13, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 106)
    - Conversations with the Governor #28: The Thornburgh Years [online], December 17, 1986 (Box 1600, Video DTV 107)
    - People's Business Interview with the Governor and Ginny Thornburgh, January 3, 1987 (Box 1600, Video DTV 108)
    - Re-election Campaign for Governor, 1982; 2.
      - Thornburgh re-election announcement, Franklin Plaza, Philadelphia, PA, March 2, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 043)
      - Reelection Campaign Fundraiser Luncheon: President Reagan speaker [online], May 14, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 045b)
      - WITF Newsmakers:1982 Election, Host John Baer, September 3, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 048)
      - Re-election Campaign for Governor Ads [online], 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 049)
      - Election Night, Philadelphia [online], November 2, 1982 (Box 1600, Video DTV 050)
  - Institute of Politics, 1987-1988; 3.
    - Thornburgh Returns to K & L, January, 1987 (Box 1600, Video DTV 109)
    - "Thornburgh Legacy" [online], April 13, 1988 (Box 1600, Video DTV 110)
  - Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; 4.
    - PBS: "McNeil-Lehrer Report": Thornburgh Named Attorney General of the United States [online], July 14, 1988 (Box 1600, Video DTV 111)
    - AG Thornburgh speaks to Department of Justice (DOJ) Employees in the Great Hall for the first time [online], October 7, 1988 (Box 1600, Video DTV 112)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) San Diego Sector, Mexican Border Patrol, San Ysidro, CA, October 24, 1988 (Box 1600, Video DTV 113)
    - Multiple TV Stations: AG Interview following Argument at the Supreme Court re Drug Testing (Burnley), November 2, 1988 (Box 1601, Video DTV 114)
    - ABC This Week with David Brinkley: AG Thornburgh and Senator Boren regarding Oliver North, January 8, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 115)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. Week, at 21st Street Ecumenical Center, Atlanta, Georgia; speech, January 16, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 116)
    - NBC Meet the Press and NBC Today Show, Multiple Topics, January 20, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 117)
    - Announcement to National Governor's Association (NGA) re funds to states for fighting drugs and crime, February 27, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 118)
    - President Bush at Glynco: Federal Law Enforcement Training Center in GA, AG accompanies; subject crime package, June 15, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 119)
    - ABC This Week with David Brinkley regarding Flag Desecration, July 2, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 120)
    - FBI Agents' Graduation and Tour, Quantico, VA, July 7, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 121)
    - Federal Bar Association, Tom Clark Award, Washington, DC, August 25, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 122)
    - PBS: "MacNeil Lehrer News Hour" regarding Columbia and Drug War [online], August 28, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 123)
    - Mutual Legal Assistance Treaty Signing Ceremony: AG and Prince Bola Ajibola of Nigeria, September 13, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 124)
    - 200th Anniversary of Office of AG: remarks of President Bush and AG Thornburgh, September 22, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 125)
    - ABC Good Morning America: regarding Soviet Union Trip, October 23, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 126)
    - CBS Nightwatch: Soviet Union Trip, October 25, 1989 (Box 1601, Video DTV 127)
    - AG statement re apprehension of Noriega at Howard Air Force Base, Panama, January 4, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 128)
    - MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour regarding Noriega, January 4, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 129)
    - C-SPAN: Employment of the Disabled, January 10, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 130)
    - Attorney General's Press Conference regarding Exxon Valdez [online], February 27, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 131)
    - AG Testimony at the hearing of the Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary House Appropriations Committee regarding Fiscal Year 1991 Appropriations, March 8, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 132)
    - AG News Conference/Boston: Crime Family Indicted, March 26, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 133)
    - Senate Judiciary Committee: Testimony, April 3, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 134)
    - CNN "Newsmaker Saturday" AG Interview regarding Crime in the USA, April 28, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 135)
    - C-SPAN: Mexican-American Attorney Generals Borders Conference, Santa Fe, NM, May 6, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 136)
    - C-SPAN: Senate Judiciary Committee: DOJ authorization testimony, May 8, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 137)
    - House Judiciary Committee, May 16, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 138)
    - Ginny Thornburgh on Dr. Schuler's "Hour of Power", May 20, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 139)
    - ABC: "This Week with David Brinkley" regarding the Civil Rights Bill, May 20, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 140)
    - U.S. Attorney Financial Institution Fraud Conference with President Bush and Attorney General Thornburgh, June 22, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 141)
    - News Conference: AG and U.S. Attorney Arnold regarding the Midwest Federal J&L indictment, June 26, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 142)
    - Heritage Foundation regarding the Rule of Law and David Brinkley Show regarding Neal Bush, July 15, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 143)
    - National Press Club: White Collar crime "Box Score on the Savings and Loans", July 25, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 144)
    - Action News: Dick Thornburgh Live regarding the Anti-Fraud Bill, July 25, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 145)
    - 1990 ALEC Convention: Luncheon Speech regarding civil rights, crime, drugs, firearms, Supreme Court nomination of David Souter, July 27, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 146)
    - Senate Banking Committee: Bank and Thrift Fraud, August 2, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 147)
    - Joint American/Russian Conference with Soviet Minister of Justice Veniamin F. Yakovlev and Attorney General Thornburgh [online], August 17, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 148)
    - C-SPAN I: Call-In Interview with the AG regarding civil rights, Supreme Court nomination/David Souter, J&L Crisis, Henry Barr, Noriega, gun control, drugs, Nazi war criminals, white collar crime, August 22, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 149)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) Speech at Boston University School of Law, September 14, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 150)
    - Press Conference on Crime Bill, September 26, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 151)
    - Attorney General with Stuart Hobson Middle School Class, October 4, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 152)
    - CBS/NBC/CNN/ABC: Attorney General's Japanese Internees Ceremony, October 9, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 153)
    - PA Broadcasters' Gold Medal Award: Dick Thornburgh Biography, October 14, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 154)
    - CNN "The World Today": Civil Rights Act, October 22, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 155)
    - Indictment Announcement: N D Texas/ New Savings and Loan Case/ Press Conference--indictment against Jarrett E. Woods, Jr., October 25, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 156)
    - AG Closing Remarks, Disability Employment Awareness Month Ceremony, October 30, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 157)
    - C-SPAN I: AG Speech before DOJ Financial Institution Fraud Enforcement Conference, November 6, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 158)
    - CNN: AG Press Conference regarding the Indictment of Mail Bomb Murderer Walter Leroy Moody, Jr., November 7, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 159)
    - Law Enforcement Television Network (LETN): AG Interview, November 13, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 160)
    - C-SPAN: Role of the Attorney General, December 27, 1990 (Box 1601, Video DTV 161)
    - The Attorney General's Awards Ceremony, Great Hall, February 8, 1991 (Box 1601, Video DTV 162)
    - ABC: AG Guest on Dr. Robert Schuller' s Hour of Power, February 10, 1991 (Box 1601, Video DTV 163)
    - Attorney General's announcement of indictments against former officers of Atlanta Branch of Banca Nazionale Del Lavoro (BNL) over Iraqi Agricultural and other Export Credits [online], February 28, 1991 (Box 1601, Video DTV 164)
    - AG Introduction of President Bush and President Bush Speech to DOJ Crime Summit, March 5, 1991 (Box 1601, Video DTV 165)